[
    {
        "front": "これ, この",
        "back": "This (near to the speaker)",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "それ, その",
        "back": "That (near to the listener)",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "あれ, あの",
        "back": "That over there (far from both listener & speaker)",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "どれ, どの",
        "back": "Which",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "ほん",
        "back": "Book",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "ファイル",
        "back": "File",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "つくえ",
        "back": "Table",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "いす",
        "back": "Chair",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "ビル",
        "back": "Building",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "なん",
        "back": "What",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "ですから",
        "back": "Therefore",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "とけい",
        "back": "Watch, Clock",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "そう です ね",
        "back": "That’s right",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "かさ",
        "back": "Umbrella",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "すごい",
        "back": "Wonderful, amazing",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "どうぞ",
        "back": "Please (While offering something to someone)",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "ありがとう",
        "back": "Casual way of saying thanks",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "よ",
        "back": "(When spoken in the end) Making an appeal to someone",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "えっと",
        "back": "Umm...",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "ここ; こちら",
        "back": "Here; (Polite)",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "そこ; そちら",
        "back": "There; (Polite)",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "あそこ; あちら",
        "back": "Over There; (Polite)",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "どこ; どちら",
        "back": "Where; (Polite)",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "じむしつ",
        "back": "Office room",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "うけつけ",
        "back": "Reception",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "かいぎしつ",
        "back": "Meeting room",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "かいだん",
        "back": "Stairs",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "でんわ",
        "back": "Telephone",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "エレベタ",
        "back": "Lift",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "いりぐち",
        "back": "Entrance",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "でぐち",
        "back": "Exit",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "しょくどう",
        "back": "Canteen",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "うえ",
        "back": "Above",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "した",
        "back": "Below",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "そと",
        "back": "Outside",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "なか",
        "back": "Inside",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "はな",
        "back": "Flowers",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "ねこ",
        "back": "Cat",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "いぬ",
        "back": "Dog",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "いえ",
        "back": "House",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "しゃちょう",
        "back": "President",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "かいちょう",
        "back": "Chairman",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぶちょう",
        "back": "Manager",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "でんわ ばんごう",
        "back": "Landline No.",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "けいたい",
        "back": "Mobile No.",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "せき",
        "back": "Seat",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "ノート",
        "back": "Notebook",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "てちょう",
        "back": "Pocket Diary",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "めいし",
        "back": "Visiting Card",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "ざっし",
        "back": "Magazine",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "じどうしゃ",
        "back": "Automobile",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "かさ",
        "back": "Umbrella",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "かぎ",
        "back": "Keys",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "しん おおさか",
        "back": "(Place Name)",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "おてあらい",
        "back": "Washroom",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "じむしょ",
        "back": "Office",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "エレベタ",
        "back": "Lift",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "くに",
        "back": "(Your) country",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "くつ",
        "back": "Shoes",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    },
    {
        "front": "けしょうしつ",
        "back": "Make-Up Room",
        "chapter": "N5 C4"
    }
]